RG 111, International Order of the King’s Daughters and Sons, Connecticut Branch
Connecticut State Library
International Order of the King’s Daughters and Sons, Connecticut Branch records
1892-1968
Connecticut State Library
International Order of the King’s Daughters and Sons. Connecticut Branch
2.5 cubic feet
The International Order of the King's Daughters and Sons was an “international, interdenominational, inter-racial [sic] organization for development of spiritual life and stimulation of Christian activities,” the Connecticut Branch is composed of a number of local “circles” which met periodically.
RG111
T001447
Historical Note
The International Order of the King's Daughters and Sons was an “international, interdenominational, inter-racial [sic] organization for development of spiritual life and stimulation of Christian activities,” the Connecticut Branch is composed of a number of local “circles” which met periodically. These circles conducted various social services including visiting the homebound and aged, reading to the blind, and fundraising for the needy. The organization also supervised various youth groups who engaged in similar social activities.
Scope and Content
The records include meeting minutes, membership rolls, scrapbooks, financial records, reports, and correspondence.
Related Material
None.
Index Terms
Organizations:
International Order of the King’s Daughters and Sons. Connecticut Branch
Subjects:
International Order of the King’s Daughters and Sons. Connecticut Branch -- Records and correspondence
Document Types:
Minutes; Scrapbooks; Correspondence; Reports; Financial records
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Records, 1892-1968
  - 1. Connecticut Branch
    - Executive Board minutes, 1896-1951; 4 volumes (Box 1)
      - 1896 February 11-1909 October 14, 1 volume (Box 1)
      - 1910 January 28-1925 January 1, 1 volume (Box 1)
      - 1925 January 23-1934 May 22, 1 volume (Box 1)
      - 1934 October 16-1951 September 18, 1 volume (Box 1)
    - Annual conventions (state) minutes, 1895-1950; 4 volumes (Box 1)
      - 1895 November 20-1911 October 12, 1 volume (Box 1)
      - 1911 October 12-1927 November 2, 1 volume (Box 1)
      - 1928 November 7-1936 October 7, 1 volume (Box 1)
      - 1937 November 3-1950 October 17, 1 volume (Box 1)
    - State Convention rolls, 1929-1942; 1 volume (Box 1)
    - Financial and membership statistics, circa 1939-1942; 1 volume (Box 1)
    - Scrapbooks, 1911-1928; 2 volumes (Box 1)
      - 1911 September-1925 January, 1 volume (Box 1)
      - 1925 January-1928 January, 1 volume (Box 1)
    - State and local officers, 1921-1934; 1 volume (Box 1)
    - Credentials committee reports, 1915-1928; 2 volumes (Box 1)
      - 1915-1922, 1 volume (Box 1)
      - 1923-1928, 1 volume (Box 1)
    - Recording Secretary's report, 1908-1927; 1 volume (Box 1)
    - Treasurer's reports, receipts, 1912-1950 (Box 2)
    - Connecticut Branch annual reports, 1928-1946 (Box 2)
    - Annual reports of circles and dues, 1942-1947 (Box 2)
    - State and County President's reports, 1941-1950 (Box 2)
    - Correspondence and Greetings at National Convention, 1935-1936 (Box 2)
    - Convention reports, 1935-1941, 1944 (Box 2)
    - Recording Secretary's report, 1928-1934 (Box 2)
  - 2. Every Day Charity Circle, Wolcott, Conn., 1896-1955 (Box 3)
  - 3. Cheerful Workers Circle, 1892-1904 (Box 4)
    - Record book, 1892-1904; 1 volume (Box 4)
  - 4. Norwich City Union, 1906-1968 (Box 4)
    - Treasurer's book, 1906 March 8-1968 January 2; 1 volume (Box 4)
    - Secretary's book, 1918 April-1967 December; 1 volume (Box 4)